

Game Programmer with experience developing mobile games for one year and have been using the Unity engine for 2 years. Understand design principles like composition over inheritance, and adopted data-driven design to easily create game levels. Learning about automization in games to increase efficiency. Love indie games, and love the indie industry even more.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Multimedia Developer

Mass Modules

2023 - Current

- · Developed 2 mini games accroding to the client's requirement.
- · Learned and interested in Kinect.

Junior Programmer

Minidragon

2021 - 2022

- · Publish game events regularly with a team.
- · Run a Discord community with dozens active players and respond to their account issues, feature requests, bug reports;
- Profile the game to improve lags and freezings. Eg applying object pooling to UI game objects to remove freezing caused by loading.
- · Develop game features like an idle game mechanics to generate higher retention for the game.

Unity developer (part-time)

2019 - 2020

Mint-asia

Develop an educational competitive game with a team of 5 members, using Photon.

CERTIFICATIONS

CS50's Introduction to Game Development

Harvard University

2023

cs50q

Complete 12 projects, mostly using Löve 2D. Teach me about concepts like Entity Component System and designs like state stack, data-driven design.

CS50x

2022

Harvard University

cs50x

Complete 18 assignments and 1 final project, for learning from C, memory, data strctures, then Python and SQL, then ends with the Internet, web development and session.

PROJECTS

Hectic Bins - A game originally made for a game jam - Ludum Dare 52. Got 112th out of 1641 submissions in the fun category as a result. Later ported to mobile and listed on Google Play.

Ninja Dash - Developed as a practice of applying design like SOLID and data-driven to a project. Improved game design sense as well.

Portfolio Reel - A short video showcasing many of my Unity projects, which the focus is much less about programming but Unity's features.

Kenneth Yu

Unity Programmer

kennethyu1224@outlook.com



<u>uyhtennek.github.io</u>



6315 6037

SKILLS

Unity & C#

Git & GitHub

Lua, Python, JavaScript

Unity Gaming Service, Firebase

Flask, Django, node.js

EDUCATION

BSc in Multimedia

LANGUAGES

Cantonese (Native)